THE ORDINARY JACKPOT
Eat it with the soup.
It's better that way.
I'll eat however I want to.
- It tastes better this way.
- Come on.
Just trust me and try it.
I like the original taste
of tuna rice balls.
Original taste, my foot.
This is how you enjoy
tteokbokki stew.
I can just add soup
to the fried rice later.
Fried rice should be eaten on its own
so the scorched rice stays crispy.
We just can't seem to see eye to eye.
- Get more pickled radish.
- Yes, ma'am.
Here you go.
Another drink?
Look, it's Yoo Ji-hyun.
I reviewed her contract
for the Laknes ad.
Just because of that,
I feel closer to her now.
Same here. Now that she's
in our company's ad
- I like her more.
- Right?
I feel bad for her.
Why did she have to get a divorce?
She lost her family,
and she'll lose her model pay.
Why would she lose her pay?
In cases like this,
the contract is usually terminated.
The ad hasn't gone public yet
so there's no need for the company
to use someone in a controversy.
EPISODE 6: PROBLEM RECOGNIZES PROBLEM
All right.
Is it hazelnut?
Of course.
You haven't forgotten.
How could I forget
your preference, Mr. Son?
So why did you want to see me?
What do you mean?
I just wanted to enjoy
a cup of coffee with you
since it's been a while.
Bullshit.
Well, it's about contract workers.
What about them?
Team 2's contract worker
seems to be doing a great job.
Yeah, he's fantastic.
Since he's doing well
you probably won't
have to worry about him.
Could you keep an eye out
for Lee Ji-hye of Team 5?
Hey.
Do you know
what your reputation at work is?
- My reputation?
- Yeah.
How is it?
It's good.
Some even call you an ace.
Gosh, that's all thanks
to what you taught me...
But why do you think
you're still an assistant manager?
If you tell me now,
I'll take it to heart.
You're a good problem solver.
The problem with that is
you only solve the internal issues.
Demands from higher-ups
conflicts among the juniors
and office politics, stuff like that.
So whether or not you can solve
a real issue at the company
remains to be seen.
I'm telling you this
because I care about you.
Don't be upset, okay?
Oh, I'm not upset at all.
Stop focusing on things
like the contract workers
and do some real work.
That will benefit you.
Yes, sir.
Hang on.
You call your team's
contract worker by her name
but the one in my team
is just a "contract worker"?
You don't even know his name
but ask me to keep
an eye out for Ji-hye?
Yoon Jeong-min.
That's his name.
Got it.
- One moment.
- Sure.
Yes, hello?
Yes.
Sorry?
- Hello, Mr. Gong.
- Hello, Mr. Yang.
Where's Gi-tae?
He hasn't come in yet.
INCOMING CALL
MR. YANG JUN-HO
Yes, I understand.
I apologize.
We should've handled it sooner.
All right, goodbye.
The Distribution Team
must be in chaos.
Their schedule is screwed up,
so they're very upset.
Is Gi-tae still not picking up?
No, he's not.
He's not the type to run away
from his own mess.
Let's figure out how to fix this.
This is the current situation.
We placed an additional order
for 300 million won
but the purchase order said
three billion won by mistake.
Laknes followed the purchase order
and sent the goods
which just arrived in Incheon.
But didn't Laknes reach out?
Surely, they would've known
there was an issue with the quantity.
We don't know that.
Let's not jump to conclusions.
Even 300 million was
a generous order.
We won't be able to handle
three billion.
If we go by retail price,
isn't that over ten billion?
That is the problem.
How should we solve it?
We'll start with
what Gi-tae didn't do.
I'll report it to Mr. Jang.
Ms. Jang, you'll come with me.
Mr. Yang and Ji-hye.
- Find Gi-tae and bring him to me.
- Yes, sir.
Mr. Gong.
May I come with you
to see Mr. Jang instead?
Well, I asked you to find Gi-tae
because you two are close.
We are close,
but this time, I'd like to...
I'll go, then.
I don't mind.
All right, then.
Okay.
Is he in?
Yes.
Come in.
Where's Park Gi-tae?
We're looking for him right now.
Aren't purchase orders
under your purview?
Didn't you check it?
The first draft was for 250 million.
After checking,
I revised it to 300 million.
I failed to check it properly
after that.
Are you proud of yourself?
I'm sorry, sir.
Did you forget Ms. Park told you
to report to her about every payment?
You reported to me,
so your job is done.
But what about me?
Do I need to report this?
If you just give us three days,
I think we can fix this.
As for getting the numbers in order
I think we can get it done
before the quarterly report.
Saying you can do it
and saying you "think" you can do it
are completely different things.
Give it to me straight.
I think we can do it.
Damn it.
Give it a shot, then.
You have three days
before I report this.
Whether I report it
as a minor issue or a disaster
is up to you two.
Yes, sir.
Did Jang Hyang-eun go to find Gi-tae?
Not you?
Yes, sir.
Lee Ji-hye went with her.
Why are you acting out of character?
Just stick to what you usually do.
Just fix this problem first.
And bring Park Gi-tae back alive.
Yes, sir.
Do you have a plan?
I think so.
Why, you little...
Feel free to rest your eyes.
No, I'm all right.
Just take it easy.
Do I make you uncomfortable?
No, not at all.
I just want to be polite.
Being comfortable doesn't mean
you'll start being rude.
Right.
How was your time in China?
It was boring.
For most employees assigned overseas
the men run wild,
while the women get bored.
All I did was work.
I see.
Is that why you came back?
Haven't you heard
the rumors about me?
What rumors?
That I fled after engaging
in corruption in China.
That I slept with a top executive,
so I got off easy.
That I'm dating someone
from another team.
That all my clothes are knockoffs.
That I'm always at
the counterfeit market in Dongdaemun.
That I make 4 million
and spend 5 million on clothes.
Those are the ones I've heard.
Haven't you heard any of them?
No, I haven't heard a single one.
I've only heard that
you're one of the best employees.
If it weren't for our team,
I probably would've quit.
If I were on another team
they would've pestered me
about if the rumors were true
and about what happened in China.
Shouldn't you say something
instead of toughing it out?
I want to do something.
But I don't know what to do.
It's hard to explain myself
when people talk behind my back.
In the end,
they'll either believe me or not.
I just have to hope
more people believe me.
Do you think Laknes
really didn't know it was an error?
There's no way they didn't know.
I know we're the ones who messed up
but it's still really annoying.
Well, what can we do?
Make one mistake,
and this world will rip you apart.
If we take the simple approach,
we just need more retailers.
It's not like a retailer
will just fall into our laps.
I actually know of one.
So Mr. Gong.
We need to make sure
the extra stock looks intentional.
Hello, Mr. Gong.
Hello, Mr. Kim.
I checked after your sudden request
for a conference call
and saw that the additional order
was quite large.
Yes, we would've appreciated it
if you had checked it sooner.
It really is a shame.
I believe
the person in charge thought
it was a regular order,
not an additional order.
Yes, since it's been two months
since our regular purchase order
they must have assumed
the next order was sent early.
Right. Well, although
this wasn't our mistake
let's try figuring it out together.
The thing is
it wasn't a mistake.
What other retailer do we have?
Our multi-brand store.
It wasn't a mistake, you say?
Could you please elaborate?
The decision was made on short notice
so we couldn't notify you.
We're launching
a multi-brand shoe store
and we want to include Laknes.
I see.
So that's the reason you made
such a large order?
Yes, we were going to send the order
after negotiating the invoice price
but there was an oversight.
You want to renegotiate the price?
The order quantity has
increased significantly
so the price should be changed
to reflect that.
By how much?
Enough for a justification.
The truth is, there's some opposition
to Laknes joining
the multi-brand store.
There's also opposition
from other brands
about selling Laknes' shoes
alongside theirs.
We sincerely apologize
for doing things out of order
but we hope Laknes can provide us
with a justification.
What is the scale
of this multi-brand store?
We'll be opening 40 locations
simultaneously.
Forty...
What if we lower the cost
of additional orders
to two billion won?
That price seems reasonable.
That should be enough justification.
But for this one order
would you be able to lower it
to 1.5 billion?
To 1.5 billion?
Will that work?
If they processed the order
knowing it was an error
they might feel somewhat guilty.
Then it just might work.
Yes.
This multi-brand shoe store
is a project that will mobilize
company-wide resources.
If Laknes agrees to help out
it'll be a huge boost for us.
And this agreement can serve
as a reminder to avoid
any future mistakes.
Very well.
We'll agree to those terms.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
This is a good opportunity for us.
I hope it is successful.
Also, if it's all right with you
we'd like to include Laknes-branded
shopping bags at the store.
It will help promote the brand.
Well, sure.
Then we'll proceed
and wait for you to send them.
- Thank you.
- All right.
THE MEETING HAS ENDED
The collective cost of shopping bags
can be around ten million won.
What is it?
You were awesome.
Do you really think that order
was for the multi-brand store?
Come on, we both know
there is no way that's true.
Sir!
Here, I got the documents.
You got this from the Port Authority?
Yes, sir.
Well...
REPORT OF PORT CARGO HANDLING RATES
AND CHARGES
Did they allow this?
This provides two extra weeks
of storage free of charge.
Everything's good now, right?
All right, then.
You have two weeks.
After that, it's not my concern.
Thank you so much, sir.
Wait, don't forget your phone.
It's been ringing all day.
Oh, right.
17 MISSED CALLS FROM
MR. YANG JUN-HO
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Ji-hye.
Ms. Jang.
So tell me.
Were you going to report back
after trying to fix it?
Yes, I figured
that's the least I could do.
What will happen to us now?
Why?
Do you think you'll get fired
over this one mistake?
Well, my getting fired
doesn't matter.
But won't this affect
our team's results?
It won't be good for Ji-hye, either.
Gi-tae, don't think like that.
Mr. Gong told me to relay a message
when we found you, Gi-tae.
Ms. Jang.
Yes, sir.
Check out the Port Authority
or the container terminal.
Gi-tae isn't the type to hide away
and drink over his mistakes.
- Yes, sir.
- And give him this message for me.
This incident was my fault.
So I'll be the one
to take accountability.
"This incident was my fault.
So I'll be the one
to take accountability.
Don't be cheeky
and try to take the blame yourself."
Those were his words.
That doesn't sound like Mr. Gong.
The sentiment is the same.
Didn't you think about
how upset Mr. Gong would be?
Because I messed up?
No, because you didn't tell him.
As soon as Mr. Gong found out
the first thing he did
was report to Mr. Jang.
Because he trusts Mr. Jang.
You treated Mr. Gong like someone
who evades responsibility
and can't solve problems.
Is that what he thinks?
Probably not.
Right.
Everyone makes mistakes at work.
So don't make a big deal of it.
Got it?
Does everyone make mistakes
this big?
Rarely.
Right.
AD MODEL CONTRACT
How fast do you need it?
He's on his way to her
with the contract
so we'll need it within the hour.
He already left with the contract?
Are you kidding me?
I know it's a big ask
but we've made up for half
of the money from the incident.
With this,
we should be able to get by.
Even so, how can you expect
a legal review
to be done in an hour?
You call it a legal review
but you're just asking
for instant approval.
We just can't miss
the window on this.
Then you should've brought
a normal contract.
I mean, what is this?
I've never even seen
or heard of such clauses.
Why are they included?
Well, I didn't write it.
I get that you're in a rush
but we have procedures to follow
and an obligation of responsibility.
If we approve this contract,
we have to explain why.
Of course, I'm well aware of that.
I'm asking for a favor.
I'm not asking without knowing that.
Your whole team is unbelievable.
Are you from Hongsung?
Yes.
Have a seat.
Thank you for coming all this way.
Not at all.
With the nice weather,
it felt like I was going on a picnic.
I see you have
a hobby in woodworking.
Working in showbiz can feel
pretty pointless sometimes.
It all seems like an illusion.
Making something with my hands
feels like it's helping improve
my mental health.
Besides, I don't have
any other hobbies.
That's all.
It's nice to see this.
Most people have hobbies
where they use things.
But you're building things instead.
So what's the plan?
Oh, right.
I'm not good at small talk.
I gave it my best shot just now.
I doubt it's good news,
so just tell me and get it over with.
Why do you think
it won't be good news?
Aren't you here to terminate
my modeling contract?
You're launching a new brand.
There's no need to use an actress
who's getting divorced as your model.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you
before signing the contract.
Marriage can be a cycle
of separation and reconciliation.
I didn't know
if we'd actually get divorced.
Besides, divorce isn't a flaw.
We don't plan
to terminate the contract.
I just came here to ask you a favor.
What is it?
Sorry, I have to check this message.
It's important.
LEGAL REVIEW COMPLETE
YOU CAN GIVE HER THE CONTRACT
My apologies.
We'd like to sign a new contract.
Please take a look
at the contract first.
Paperwork gives me a headache
these days.
Can my lawyer look at it
and give you a call?
Sure.
In that case,
could you just check Article 8?
What's in Article 8?
ARTICLE 8: MORALITY CLAUSE
We revised the morality clause.
As you can see
we've included a morality clause
for both parties.
The clause is usually included
in case of a model's controversy.
But there are also many cases
of brand controversy harming models.
However, since we're the employer
the penalty fee amount is different.
We'd appreciate your understanding
on that matter.
You want to include
a bilateral morality clause?
Is it even allowed?
Your divorce shouldn't be considered
a controversy.
If you're worried about
contract termination due to that
then I believe
the contract is unfair.
Thus, we revised the clause.
So I'll just ask you one question.
Were you at fault
for your divorce?
We were both at fault.
However, to answer your question
I did nothing wrong.
That's all I needed to know.
Let's sign the contract.
If you wanted to terminate,
I would have no excuses.
Instead, you came
with an even better contract.
So what would you like me to do?
Please attend your divorce hearing.
I assume you want me
to wear Laknes's shoes?
Yes.
You're something else.
I'm fully aware that it's a big ask.
Is that why you came
with the revised contract?
I'll do it.
I'm also aware of how difficult it is
to write a contract like this.
Thank you.
Mr. Gong.
Would you consider being my manager?
I'm serious.
I'll pay more
than your current salary.
Will you consider it?
No.
I was just thinking
of a polite way to say this.
Just say it.
I wasn't polite, either.
I'm sorry
but I have money too.
SEOUL FAMILY COURT
WHAT A SIMPLE, YET ELEGANT LOOK
WALKING TO COURT LIKE IT'S A RUNWAY
#YOOJIHYUN
WHAT BRAND ARE HER SHOES?
THE NEW LINE FROM LAKNES
I ALREADY GOT A PAIR
LAKNES NEW COLLECTION!
THE PERFECT MONOTONE LOOK
THE SHOES COMPLETE THE LOOK
SO PRETTY I'M SPEECHLESS
#YOOJIHYUN #GODDESS
BOOKMARKING THIS
I WANT TO COPY HER LOOK
CAN ANYONE TELL ME
WHERE HER SHOES ARE FROM?
LAKNES, I'M BUYING A PAIR TODAY
BLACK MARY JANE PUMPS
ORDER COMPLETE
TOTAL OFFLINE AND ONLINE SALES
JULY: 3,893,858,858 WON
AUGUST: 4,337,122,530 WON
SALES INCREASE: 443,263,672
GROWTH RATE: 11%
SEPTEMBER,
SALES INCREASE, GROWTH RATE
I've never seen sales increase
by 1400% in a single month.
- Me neither.
- Same here.
What if they made a mistake like me
and added an extra zero?
You little...
I'll hit you too.
Join in, Ji-hye.
I'm okay.
Come on, you suffered a lot.
Don't regret missing out later.
It's okay, Ji-hye. Hit me.
- What do I do?
- What else?
Time to leave him alone
and get back to work.
Please, Mr. Gong. I'm sorry.
Shall we, Mr. Gong?
- It's 1400%.
- You little...
Please.
- What are you doing?
- Seriously.
I'm sorry, sir.
Come with me.
The vice president?
Why, all of a sudden?
I don't know, either.
All I did was report
the sales growth numbers.
The director was summoned right away.
That was 30 minutes ago.
Do you think he'll reprimand us?
It wouldn't be weird
if he reprimanded us
nor would it be weird
if he praised us.
What do you think he'll do?
If he reprimands me,
I'll listen calmly.
And if he praises me,
I'll listen humbly.
So you don't mind either way?
He's free to judge it
however he sees fit.
If I went back in time
I wouldn't do anything differently.
So it doesn't matter to me.
What is it?
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Come in.
Have a seat.
Mr. Gong.
Is it your first time here?
Yes, sir.
Why do you think I called you?
I'm not sure, sir.
You must have some idea.
Our sales increased significantly,
but it was due to a mistake.
So I came expecting a reprimand.
I was curious.
You successfully launched a brand
no one else wanted to take on.
We sent you to Italy
to cut out the traitor
but you practically turned him
into our subsidiary instead.
You made a mistake with the order
but now it looks like
you had the foresight
to preorder
before the brand took off.
That's enough to pique my curiosity.
I've come up
with two possible conclusions.
You're either overqualified
for the position
or you're overstepping your role.
Why don't you take this on?
Recently, we got a tip-off
about corruption in Sales Division 2.
So we reprimanded them.
But not long after,
we got another tip-off.
We found a cockroach in our house
so we quickly blocked the drains
and sprayed pesticide
but it was of no use.
The house is already infested.
In the end,
the Audit Team decided to step up.
But they lack hands-on experience.
I'd like you to help them.
Well...
With all due respect
if another division
conducts the audit
there will be a lot of pushback
from Division 2.
That's why I'm leaving it to you.
Go make some noise.
Can you do a good job?
I'll work hard.
Work hard, of course.
Doing a good job is a given.
Watch your expression.
There's nothing more annoying
than an auditor
going around with a smile.
Yes, ma'am.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
If another division
conducts the audit
there will be a lot of pushback
from Division 2.
That's why I'm leaving it to you.
Go make some noise.
The branch was deeply corrupt.
Word is, Jang Hyang-eun
was at the center of it all.
I'm sure you have
many questions for me.
Why haven't you asked me anything?
Over here.
Why did you ask to meet outside?
I wanted to speak with you privately.
I'm nervous now.
I doubt it. I know you're not
the type to get nervous.
Let me rephrase. I'm concerned.
Have a taste.
The coffee here is delicious.
Ms. Jang, I want to ask you a favor.
Sure, what is it?
There will be an audit
of Sales Division 2 soon.
I will be assisting them
on the ground.
A sales division is auditing
another sales division?
That's right.
There will be a lot of backlash.
You know that, right?
Of course.
If it's okay with you,
I'd like you to join me.
What do you say?
You know, I like Gi-tae more now
after the incident.
Because he ran around
trying to fix it himself?
Yes, he did all he could
to solve it on his own.
I'm the same way.
So it was nice to see him do that.
Yes, it was impressive.
However...
Once I became a team leader
I was assigned tasks
I couldn't complete on my own.
I confidently said
I'd take the Laknes project
but Mr. Yang is the one
who actually resolved things.
I can't complete this task
on my own, either.
I need your help, Ms. Jang.
Mr. Gong.
Why do you think
I came back from China?
Don't you think
I was involved in the corruption?
I don't think
you were completely uninvolved.
Then how can I join the Audit Team?
Were you involved in corruption?
I guess you signed
a non-disclosure agreement.
In that case, just listen.
In my opinion
I don't think
you committed corruption.
But you're involved in it somehow.
Whether by choice or circumstance,
you might've played a role.
I think you're staying silent
out of courtesy to your colleagues.
So this is my conclusion.
You're the whistleblower, aren't you?
I know that reporting your colleague
weighs on you.
I've also dared to imagine
the things you endured
after blowing the whistle.
You had to stay silent
in the face of everyone's whispers.
And you had no way
to explain yourself.
Let people talk if they want to.
How about we just do
what is in our power?
Do this with me.
I'll help you carry the weight
on your shoulders.
Are you asking me
to help me feel better?
Well, it's not just that.
They say it takes one to know one.
I thought you'd be well-versed
since you have experience with this.
THE ORDINARY JACKPOT
2 MONTHS AGO, CHINA
Have you made up your mind?
Yes.
Do you know
what being a whistleblower entails?
I'm well aware.
No.
You have no clue.
For starters,
you must have a spotless record.
Not just professionally, but in life.
Even something as minor as littering
will be used to criticize you
and say you're no better.
But sure, let's say
you've never littered even once.
Do you think people
will call you a hero?
No way.
No matter the reason
it's instinctual to avoid someone
who betrays their colleague.
Even more so in a small,
crowded country like Korea!
Moving forward
no one will want to work with you.
Just know that.
Be honest with me.
Did you really not know
what we were doing?
Come on. You knew, didn't you?
A clever girl like you?
You just looked the other way.
So we gave you luxury stuff
to keep looking the other way!
You knew we used company funds
to hire your housekeeper.
Yes, I knew everything.
Come on!
Then why?
Why are you doing this?
Do you mind if I have a smoke?
What?
I'm getting angry.
Do you know why I'm angry?
You used the company's work
for personal profit.
You're even blatantly
embezzling company funds.
And now you're asking me
why I want to come forward?
Are you kidding me?
Of course, I'm not perfect, either.
Sure, I've littered before.
And as you said, I caught on
that you were using company funds
to butter me up.
So I tried to let it slide.
But I just couldn't.
The longer this goes on,
the more I'll struggle.
Why do you work, sir?
As for me
I've done nothing but work
since I grew up.
I have no hobbies.
I don't even work out.
But...
If the work is lousy
that also makes me lousy.
That's why I'm doing this.
I don't want to be lousy.
I need to quit smoking.
Subtitles by Eunice Kim